Guide to the McGraw-Hill Marketing Information Center Vertical File, 1948-1991
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Alphabetical, Topical, Keyword Index
  Information Systems, management: ADM 0:2-7.2.6
  Innovators: ADM 0:2-7.13.1
  Input/Output Analysis: MKT 50:2-1.22
  Inquiries: ADV 45 (*)
  Inquiry Analyses
  A.E. Early/Meldrum and Fewsmith/Republic Steel/Media-Scope Analysis of Business Paper Inquiries: ADV 45:5-2
  Dr. Starch's Analysis of Twelve Million Inquiries: ADV 45:5-1
  Inquiry Analysis as a Media Selection Factor: ADV 45:3
  Inquiry Costs: ADV 45:4
  Inquiry Evaluation, Handling and Follow-up: ADV 45:2 (*)
  Inquiry Response, seasonal: ADV 45:1-1
  Inquiry Stimulation Elements, couponing, etc.: ADV 45:5
  Inserts and Spreads: ADV 50:8-3
  Inside Sales Forces: SAL 10:4-2
  Integrated Distribution, international: IOP 10:1-2
  INTERNATIONAL (see alphabetized keywords followed by descriptors international or overseas, e.g. Licensing, overseas): IOP (*)
  Advertising and Communications, by country: IOP 10:2-2 (*)
  Business Fundamentals: IOP 5 (*)
  Comparative Management: IOP 5:6 (*)
  Economic Indicators, N.E.C.: IOP 0:6-3
  Operations: practices, problems, principles, procedures and strategies: IOP 10:2-1
  Interviewers/Interviewing, marketing research: MKT 50:2-2 (*)
  Interviewing, personnel: ADM 0:2-8.9
  Interviewing, sales: SAL 35:1-2
  Investments Overseas, U.S.: IOP 0:2-1
  Investor/Shareholder Relations: ADM 0:2-10.18
  Irritation in Advertising: ADV 25:5
  Issue Advertising: ADV 50:4-3.2
  J
  Job Descriptions: ADM 0:2-8.15
  Job Descriptions, sales: SAL 35:1-3
  Job Enrichment: ADM 0:2-8.10
  Job Posting: ADM 0:2-8.15
  Job Rotation: ADM 0:2-8.21.8
  Job Satisfaction, salespersons: SAL 15:3
  Joint Ventures Overseas: IOP 5:1-2
  K
  Key Account Selling: SAL 40:9-1
  KNOW Handbooks (NIAA now B/PAA): ADV 40:1-2
  L
  LAFTA (ALALC) (Latin American Free Trade Association): IOP 0:3-11
  Labels: ADV 35:4-5
  Laboratory of Advertising Performance (LAP) Indexes: ADV 40:4
  Language Usage: ADM 0:2-7.2.7
  Law of Diminishing Returns: ADV 50:1-1
  Latin Squares: MKT 50:2-1.23
  Law, international: IOP 5:5 (*)
  Leading Advertisers in Business Publications (ABP): ADV 55:1-1.3
  Leading Advertisers in Business Publications (Business Marketing): ADV 55:1-2.3
  Leading National Advertisers, Inc.: ADV 55:3-3 (*)
  Learning Process: ADM 0:2-8.21.9
  Legal Aspects of Advertising: ADV 30
  Legal Aspects of Marketing: MKT 35 (*)
  Legislative/Government Relations (PR): ADM 0:2-10.19
  Length of Copy: ADV 50:4-3.21
  Letter Costs: ADM 0:2-7.2.13
  Liability, agency: ADV 5:5-1
  Liability, product: MKT 35:5
  Libraries, corporate: ADM 0:2-10.20
  Licensing (Franchising): MKT 20:4
  Licensing, overseas: IOP 5:5-3
  Licensing Practices, as a marketing legal process: MKT 35:4
  Lie Detectors in Employment: ADM 0:2-8.11
  Life Cycles, magazines: ADV 35:4-6.1
  Life Cycles, product: MKT 60:2-2
  Life of an Advertisement: ADV 50:2-4
  Linear and Non-Linear Programming: MKT 50:2-1.24
  Linguistic Coding: MKT 50:2-2.1
  List Building, Cleaning and Maintenance: ADV 35:3-9.1
  List Control, computerized: ADV 35:3-9.2
  List Houses and Reference Sources: ADV 35:3-9.5
  List House Catalogs: ADV 35:3-9.5
  List Security: ADV 35:3-9.3
  List Testing and Research: ADV 35:3-9.4
  Listening: ADM 0:2-7.2.8
  Listening, salespersons: SAL 5:6-8
  Listening, Speaking, Writing (in combination): ADM 0:2-7.2.8.1
  Logical Flow Analysis: MKT 50:2-1.25
  Logos, corporate: ADM 0:2-10.21
  Longitudinal Analysis: MKT 50:2-1.26
  Lost Sales: SAL 40:7
  Low-Pressure Selling: SAL 40:8
  M
  Magazines, general: ADV 35:4-6 (*)
  Mail Surveys: MKT 50:2-3 (*)
  Mailing Lists, direct mail: ADV 35:3-9 (*)
  Major Customer Selling: SAL 40:9-1
  Make or Buy Decisions: MKT 40:4-3
  MANAGEMENT
  Advertising: MKT 40:1-2.1 (*)
  Brand: MKT 40:1-3.1
  Budget: ADM 0:2-6.1
  Chief Marketing Executive: MKT 40:1-1.1
  Circulation: ADV 50:5-4.2
  Communications, external and internal: ADM 0:2-10 (*)
  Comparative: IOP 5:6
  Consumer Affairs: ADM 0:2-10.8
  Corporate Secretaries: ADM 0:2-3
  Customer Service: MKT 5:2-3
  Distribution: MKT 20:8
  Economics: ADM 0:2-4 (*)
  Ethnics/Minorities: ADM 0:2-7.8
  Executive: ADM 0:2-5 (*)
  External Affairs: ADM 0:2-10 (*)
  Field Sales: SAL 10:2
  Financial: ADM 0:2-6 (*)
  Financial/Credit, in marketing: MKT 40:1-4
  General: ADM 0:2-7 (*)
  Human Resource: ADM 0:2-8.8
  Human Resource, global scale: IOP 5:6-3
  Information Systems and Retrieval: ADM 0:2-7.2.6
  International: IOP 5:6 (*)
  Advertising/Marketing: IOP 10:3 (*)
  Comparative: IOP 5:6 (*)
  Marketing Research: IOP 10:3-2
  Inventory: MKT 20:5
  Marketing: MKT 40 (*)
  Marketing/Communications: MKT 40:1-2 (*)
  Marketing Research: MKT 40:1-5
  Marketing Research, international: IOP 10:3-2
  Materials: MKT 40:1-3.2
  Matrix: ADM 0:2-7.14
  Minorities/Ethnics: ADM 0:2-7.8
  Overseas, concepts and styles: ADM 0:2-7.17
  Participative: ADM 0:2-7.18
  Personnel: ADM 0:2-8 (*)
  Presidents: ADM 0:2-2
  Product: MKT 40:1-3.1
  Production: MKT 40:1-3.3
  Project: MKT 40:1-3.3
  Public Affairs/Relations: ADM 0:2-10 (*)
  Research and Development: ADM 0:2-4.15.3.1 (*)
  Results-Oriented: ADM 0:2-7.1
  Risk: ADM 0:2-11
  Sales: SAL 10 (*)
  Sales Promotion: MKT 40:1-7
  Small Business: ADM 0:2-4.16.2
  Specialists vs. Generalists: ADM 0:2-7.13.4
  Task Force: ADM 0:2-7.25
  Technical: ADM O:2-7.13.5
  Territory, sales: SAL 10:5-5
  Traffic: MKT 20:8
  Transportation: MKT 20:8
  Women, in Management: ADM 0:2-7.28
  Management by Objectives (MBO): ADM 0:2-7.12
  Management Types, N.E.C.: ADM 0:2-7.13
  Manners, salespersons: SAL 5:6-3
  Manpower Planning: ADM 0:2-8.8
  Manuals, financial: ADM 0:2-6.4
  Manufacturers' Agents and Representatives: MKT 20:10 (*)
  Maps, marketing: MKT 50:7-6
  Market Analysis and Sales Forecasting: MKT 50:2-4 (*)
  Marketcentering Concept: MKT 5:2-6
  Market Research Departments: MKT 40:2-3
  Marketing Research Staff: MKT 40:1-5.1
  Market Segmentation: MKT 50:2-4.2 (*)
  Market Share Measurement: MKT 50:2-4.3
  MARKETING (see also alphabetized keywords followed by descriptor marketing; for example: Women, in marketing; Information and Intelligence Systems, marketing; Metrication in Marketing; Minorities, in marketing, etc.)
  Audits: MKT 10:1-1
  Communications: MKT 5:2-7
  Communications, international: IOP 10:2 (*)
  Concepts: MKT 5 (*)
  Department Organization: MKT 40:2 (*)
  Directors, agency: ADV 5:10-5
  Industrial vs. Consumer: MKT 0:3 (*)
  Information, international sources: IOP 10:3-2.1.1
  Information Sources (see writeup at beginning of the Marketing Series)
  Information Systems: MKT 40:5
  Intelligence Systems: MKT 40:5 (*)
  International: IOP 10 (*)
  Issues, historical and contemporary: MKT 0:1
  Management: MKT 40 (*)
  Management, international: IOP 10:3 (*)
  Marketing/Communications Departments: MKT 40:2-1
  Marketing in ... by country and/or region: IOP 10:4 (*)
  Marketing Mix Concept: MKT 5:2-7
  Research: MKT 50 (*)
  Research Techniques, international: IOP 10:3-2.1
  Role and General Theory: MKT 0 (*)
  Science or Process?: MKT 0:2
  Services, agency: ADV 5:12-1
  Markov Processes: MKT 50:2-1.27
  Mass Media: ADV 35:4 (*)
  Mass Media, overseas: IOP 10:2-7.5
  Matchbooks: ADV 35:4-7
  Mathematical Models in the Media Planning/Selection Process: ADV 50:5-3
  Mechanized Selling: ADV 35:1-4
  Media Buying, Evaluation, Planning and Selection: ADV 50:5 (*)
  Media Buying, Planning and Selection, in international marketing: IOP 10:2-8 (*)
  Media Comparability Council (MCC) Media Data Form Commentary: ADV 50:5-3.1.1.1
  Media Data Forms, N.E.C.: ADV 50:5-3.1.2
  Media Departments, agency: ADV 5:12-3
  Media Directors, corporate: MKT 40:1-2.1.5
  Media Kits: SAL 5:5
  Media Planning, campaigns: ADV 20
  Media Planning Checklists: ADV 50:5-2
  Media Publicity/Press Releases: ADM 0:2-10.22
  Media Relations (PR): ADM 0:2-10.23
  Media Research, suggested standards/disclosure forms: ADV 50:5-5.10.6
  Media Salespersons: SAL 5:5
  Media-Sponsored Research/Promotion, as a media buying, selection aid: ADV 50:5-5.10 (*)
  Media Tours: ADM 0:2-10.23
  Media Trends (Doyle Dane Bernbach): ADV 55:3-2
  Medical Departments, company: ADM 0:2-8.7
  Meeting Sites, directories of: ADM 0:2-7.2.5.1
  Meeting the Press: ADM 0:2-10.23
  Meetings, annual: ADM 0:2-10.24
  Meetings, employee: ADM 0:2-10.25
  Meetings, general management: ADM 0:2-7.2.5
  Meetings, sales: SAL 25 (*)
  Customer/Dealer Meetings: SAL 25:1-1
  Meeting Follow-Up: SAL 25:1-2
  Planning, Staging, Conducting, N.E.C.: SAL 25:1
  Small Meetings: SAL 25:1-3
  Memory (learning process): ADM 0:2-8.21.9
  Memory for Advertising: ADV 50:2-1.1
  Memory Training, salespersons: SAL 5:6-6
  Mentoring: ADM 0:2-8.21.6
  Merchandising Departments, agency: ADV 5:12-4
  Merchandising, marketing: MKT 0:5
  Merchandising the Advertising Program: ADV 50:6 (*)
  Mergers, agency: ADV 5:6-2
  Mergers and Acquisitions: ADM 0:2-4.2.3 (*)
  Divestment/Divestiture: ADM 0:2-4.2.3.2
  Effect of Mergers on Advertising: ADM 0:2-4.2.3.1
  FTC and the Conference Board Announcements and Statistical Reports: ADM 0:2-4.10
  Planning, Actions, Effects: ADM 0:2-4.2.3
  Strategies and Tactics for Fighting a Takeover: ADM 0:2-4.2.3.3
  Metamarketing: MKT 0:4
  Metrication in Marketing: MKT 15 (*)
  Microencapsulation: ADV 50:9-7
  Migration of Industry: The Geography of Manufacturing: ADM 0:2-4.11
  Military Advertising: MKT 70:20-1.1
  Military/Industrial Marketing Differences: MKT 70:4
  Military Marketing: The Defense Procurement System: MKT 70:2
  Military-Theme Copy: ADV 50:4-3.22
  Minorities
  as Board Members: ADM 0:2-1.3
  marketing to: MKT 50:2-4.2.1.2
  Mobility, executive: ADM 0:2-8.21.13.1
  Modeling in Marketing: MKT 40:4-5
  Models and Modeling, financial: ADM 0:2-6.5
  Models in Copy: ADV 50:4-3.32
  Morrill Study: ADV 40:2-4.1
  Motivating Employees: ADM 0:2-8.12
  Motivation, salespersons: SAL 15:5
  Motivational Research: MKT 50:2-1.2
  Multidimensional Analysis: MKT 50:2-1.28
  Multinational Corporations: IOP 5:2 (*)
  Multipagers: ADV 50:8-3
  Multiple Insertions in Same Issue: ADV 50:7-5
  Multivariate Analysis: MKT 50:2-1.29
  Murphy's Laws: ADM 0:2-7.15
  N
  NAFTA (North American Free Trade Area): IOP 0:3-12
  NORDEK (The Nordic Council): IOP 0:3-13
  Name Changes, corporate: ADM 0:2-10.26
  Name Changing/Restyling/Relaunching, publications: ADV 35:1-5
  National Accounts: Selling, Servicing, Managing: SAL 40:9
  NETAPPS Study (Dr. Daniel Starch): ADV 40:2-4.2
  New Business Development, agency: ADV 5:9
  New Business Development, sales: SAL 40:11
  New Medium Considerations, in media selection: ADV 50:5-5.8
  New Product Development and Introduction: MKT 60 (*)
  New Product Introduction, overseas: IOP 10:1-3
  New Product Introduction, using direct mail: ADV 35:3-7
  New Product Marketing: MKT 60:2 (*)
  New Yardsticks of Media Value (also known as the 18 Company Study and the Cooperative Readership Study): ADV 40:3-3
  Newsletter-Form Copy: ADV 50:4-3.24
  Newsletters/House Organs, internal and external: ADM 0:2-10.15
  Newspaper Supplements: ADV 35:4-8.1
  Newspapers: ADV 35:4-8
  Newsstand Sales: ADV 50:5-4.10.1
  No Advertising (ideas of what it would be like if there was no advertising): ADV 0:2-1
  Number of Ads Seen Daily: ADV 55:4-2
  O
  OCAM (Organization Commune Africaine et Malgache): IOP 0:3-14
  OD (Organizational Development): ADM 0:1-2
  Objections: sales, overcoming: SAL 40:10
  Objectives and Results (ABP O&R series and similar ABP studies): ADV 40:2-1.2
  Objectives, setting advertising: ADV 40:1 (*)
  Obsolescence, product: MKT 60:2-3
  Open House: ADM 0:2-10.7.1
  Operational Research: ADM 0:2-7.16
  Opinion Leader Interviewing: MKT 50:2-2.2
  Organization, corporate; Standards and Practices: ADM 0:1 (*)
  Organization, informal: ADM 0:1-4
  Organization Men/Women: ADM 0:2-7.13.2
  Organizational Charting: ADM 0:1-1
  Organizational Development (OD): ADM 0:1-2
  Outdoor Advertising: ADV 35:4-9
  Out-of-Home, media: ADV 35:4-10
  Overseas Licensing: IOP 5:5-3
  Overseas Operations, financial aspects: IOP 5:3 (*)
  P
  PARM (ARF) Study: ADV 40:3-4.2.1
  PERKS: ADM 0:2-8.4.4
  PERT: ADM 0:2-7.4.2
  PIMS Project: MKT 50:2-4.1.1
  Packaging as a Marketing Mechanism: MKT 75
  Page Size (total area): ADV 50:8-4
  Paid vs. Free Circulation: ADV 50:5-4.9
  Paid vs. Free Circulation: Tide Series: ADV 50:5-4.9.1
  Paperwork Control: ADM 0:2-7.4.1
  Part-Time Workers: ADM 0:2-8.19
  Pareto's Principle: ADM 0:2-7.15
  Pass-Along Reading: ADV 40:3-7.3
  Patents and Patenting: ADM 0:2-10.27
  Pensions: Funding and Plans: ADM 0:2-8.13
  People Switching, agency turnover: ADV 5:10-11
  Percent of Sales by Channel of Distribution: MKT 20:6
  Percent of Sales Invested in Advertising: ADV 10:4 (*)
  Performance Appraisal: ADM 0:2-8.14
  PERSONNEL MANAGEMENT AND RELATIONS (see alphabetized keywords dealing with personnel topics; e.g. Job Enrichment; Suggestion Systems, etc.): ADM 0:2-8 (*)
  Peter/Paul Principles: ADM 0:2-7.19
  Petrodollars: IOP 0:1-3
  Philanthropy, corporate: ADM 0:2-10.28
  Photographs vs. Artwork: ADV 50:9-8
  Physical Distribution and P.D. Management: MKT 20:7
  Planning
  Advertising: ADV 20
  Campaign and Media: ADV 20
  Corporate, strategic: ADM 0:2-9 (*)
  Financial: ADM 0:2-6.2
  Marketing: MKT 50:2-4.1 (*)
  Methods (PERT, CPM, RAMPS, etc.): ADM 0:2-7.4.2
  Profit: ADM 0:2-6.6
  Sales Call: SAL 10:5-1.1
  Plant Location and Site Selection: ADM 0:2-10.7.2
  Plant Site Selection, overseas: IOP 5:1-3
  Plant Tours: ADM 0:2-10.7.1
  Point-of-Purchase (In-Store): ADV 35:4-11
  Political Activism: ADM 0:2-10.19
  Political Copy: ADV 50:4-3.25
  Pooled Marketing Concept: MKT 5:2-8
  Position Descriptions: ADM 0:2-8.15
  Position Values, in advertising: ADV 50:7 (*)
  Positioning Concept: MKT 5:2-9
  Postcards: ADV 35:4-12
  Postmark Advertising: ADV 35:4-13
  Preference Studies, as a media selection aid: ADV 50:5-5.10.3
  Preference Study Research Techniques: MKT 50:2-3.3
  Presentations:
  Agency: ADV 5:9
  Media Sales: SAL 5:5
  Sales: SAL 40:12
  President Directory (Japan): IOP 0:7-4
  Presidents and CEOs: ADM 0:2-2
  Press Releases: ADM 0:2-10.22
  Price Cutting: MKT 55:3
  Price in Copy: ADV 50:4-3.26
  Price Discrimination: MKT 55:4
  Price Raising: MKT 55:5
  Price Resistance, in selling: SAL 40:10-1
  Price Waterhouse Guides to Agency Accounting Controls: ADV 5:5-2.1
  Prices/Earnings Around the World: IOP 10:3-3
  Pricing: MKT 55 (*)
  Pricing, new product: MKT 60:2-4
  Pricing Under Conditions of Economic Uncertainty: MKT 55:6
  Print vs. Electronic (media communication effectiveness): ADV 35:5
  Probability Theory: MKT 50:2-1.30
  Problem-Solving Conferences: ADM 0:2-7.2.5.2
  Problem Staffers, sales: SAL 15:5-5
  Product Copy: ADV 50:4-3.27
  Product Life Cycles: MKT 60:2-2
  Product Obsolescence, Deletion, Phase-Out: MKT 60:2-3
  Production Costs: ADV 50:5-5.4
  Production Wizards: ADM 0:2-7.13.3
  Productivity: federal, state, municipal: ADM 0:2-4.12.2
  Productivity, in marketing: MKT 30
  Productivity, N.E.C.: ADM 0:2-4.12
  Products featured (number in ad): ADV 50:9-10
  Profit Planning: ADM 0:2-6.6
  Profits:
  Business Week's surveys of corporate performance: the Corporate Scoreboard: ADM 0:2-4.13.1
  Dun & Bradstreet, Inc. Cost of Doing Business ... (Key Business Ratios; annual): ADM 0:2-4.13.3
  McGraw-Hill Department of Economics: Annual Survey of Corporate Profit Trends (discontinued): ADM 0:2-4.13.2
  Profits: their place in economy: ADM 0:2-4.13
  Programmed Instruction: ADM 0:2-8.21.9.1
  Project X (DAGMAR): ADV 40:1-1
  Projective Techniques: MKT 50:2-1.31
  Promotion, distributor: MKT 20:9-6
  Promotion, new product: MKT 60:2-7
  Promotion, sales: SAL 30 (*)
  Promotional Criteria (Personnel): ADM 0:2-8.21.10
  Property Rights, international: IOP 5:5-2
  Prospecting, sales: SAL 40:11
  Psychographics: MKT 50:2-1.32
  Psychological Testing, sales: SAL 35:1-1
  PUBLIC AFFAIRS/RELATIONS (see alphabetized keywords dealing with PR; for example: Name Changes, corporate; Annual Reports, etc.): ADM 0:2-10 (*)
  Public Affairs/Relations, international: IOP 10:2-12
  Pupil Dilation: ADV 50:9-15
  Pulsing, in advertising: ADV 50:2-3
  Purchasing Agents/Managers/Departments: MKT 65:2 (*)
  Purchasing Committees/Groups: MKT 65:3
  Purchasing Patterns: MKT 65 (*)
  Purchasing Practices, industrial (how industry buys): MKT 65:1 (*)
  Q
  Quality Circles: ADM 0:2-4.12
  Quality Control, product: MKT 35:5
  Questionnaire Construction: MKT 50:2-3.3
  Queuing Theory: MKT 50:2-1.33
  Quotas, sales: SAL 10:5-4
  RAMPS: ADM 0:2-7.4.2
  Radio, as an advertising medium: ADV 35:4-2.1
  Rankings of Top Companies, Worldwide: IOP 0:7 (*)
  Rankings of U.S. Corporations
  Black Enterprise: The Top 100 Black Businesses (annual): ADM 0:2-4.14.1
  Financial World: America's Top Growth Companies (annual): ADM 0:2-4.14.2
  Forbes: Annual Report on American Industry: ADM 0:2-4.14.3
  Forbes: The Forbes 500s (The Dimensions of American Business): ADM 0:2-4.14.3.1
  Fortune: The Fortune Directory of the 500 Largest U.S. Corporations (annual): ADM 0:2-4.14.4
  Fortune: The Fortune Directory of the Second 500 Largest Industrial Corporations (annual; suspended in 1983): ADM 0:2-4.14.4.1
  Fortune: The Fortune Directory of the 50 Top Non-Inudstrial Companies (annual; suspended in 1983): ADM 0:2-4.14.4.2
  Fortune: The Fortune Service 500 (expanded ranking of the 50 Top Non-Industrial Corporations): ADM 0:2-4.14.4.3
  Inc.: Inc., 100: ADM 0:2-4.14.5
  Ward's Directory of Largest U.S. Corporations: ADM 0:2-4.14.6
  Ward's Leading Private Companies: ADM 0:2-4.14.6.1
  Other Rankings, N.E.C.: ADM 0:2-4.14.7
  Rate Discounting: ADV 50:5-5.2
  Rate Trends (circulation) Association of National Advertisers (ANA): ADV 50:5-4.5
  Rates/Costs Predictions and Indexes, past, present and future: ADV 50:5-5.3 (*)
  Reach and Frequency: ADV 50:5-4.11
  Readership: ADV 40:3 (*)
  Readership, direct mail: ADV 35:3-10
  Readership Levels Throughout a Publication: ADV 40:3-5
  Readership Study Research Techniques: MKT 50:2-3.3
  Reading: ADM 0:2-7.2.9
  Reading Environment: ADV 40:3-7 (*)
  Reading Habits: ADV 40:3-6 (*)
  Reading, salespersons: SAL 5:6-7
  Recalls, product: MKT 35:6
  Recession Economy, advertising in: ADV 0:3-1
  Reciprocity: MKT 65:4
  Recognition Research Techniques: MKT 50:2-3.3
  Recruiting, Selection and Training: sales: SAL 35 (*)
  Recruitment Copy: ADV 50:4-3.7
  Recruitment for Marketing/Communications: MKT 40:3 (*)
  Recruitment (Personnel): ADM 0:2-8.16
  Recruitment, sales: SAL 35 (*)
  Recruitment, Training and Development; agency: ADV 5:10-7
  Regional/Demographic Editions, in media selection: ADV 50:5-5.9
  Regional Trade Groupings: IOP 0:3 (*)
  Regression Analysis: MKT 50:2-1.34
  Relocation (Personnel): ADM 0:2-8.21.13.1
  Renegotiation: MKT 70:2-1
  Renewals, circulation: ADV 50:5-4.12
  Repeat Ad Study (IARI/CMC): ADV 50:2-4.1
  Repetition, in advertising: ADV 50:2-4
  Representatives: overseas, selecting: IOP 5:1-4
  Reports, annual and quarterly: ADM 0:2-10.29
  Request Circulation: ADV 50:5-4.13
  Research
  Advertising: ADV 40 (*)
  Departments, agency: ADV 5:12-6
  Departments, marketing: MKT 40:2-3
  Guidelines for Buying: MKT 50:3
  Marketing: MKT 50 (*)
  Marketing ... by country and/or region: IOP 10:4 (*)
  Public Relations: ADM 0:2-10.30
  Researcher/Management Relations: MKT 50:5
  Selling management on the value of: MKT 50:5
  Staff, agency: ADV 5:10-8
  Staff, marketing: MKT 40:1-5.1
  Techniques, international marketing: IOP 10:3-2.1
  Techniques, marketing: MKT 50:2 (*)
  Research and Development
  Battelle Memorial Institute; Columbus Division series: Probable Levels of R&D Expenditures in (year): Forecast and Analysis: ADM 0:2-4.15.1.1
  McGraw-Hill Department of Economics: Annual Survey of Pollution Control Expenditures: ADM 0:2-4.15.1.3
  McGraw-Hill Department of Economics: Business Plans for Research and Development Expenditures (annual): ADM 0:2-4.15.1.2
  McGraw-Hill Department of Economics: Survey of Technological Breakthroughs and Widespread Application of Significant Technical Developments (discontinued): ADM 0:2-4.15.1.4
  National Science Foundation: National Patterns of R&D Resources; Funds and Manpower in the U.S. and Surveys of Science Resources: ADM 0:2-4.15.1.5
  Budgeting, Funding, Financial Control, and Resource Allocation of R&D: ADM 0:2-4.15.4
  Corporate/Marketing - R&D Interface: ADM 0:2-4.15.5
  R&D Organization and Management: ADM 0:2-4.15.3
  R&D Philosophies: ADM 0:2-4.15.2
  R&D Staff: ADM 0:2-4.15.3.1
  Resident Salespeople: SAL 10:4-4
  Resistances in Selling, overcoming: SAL 40:10
  Response Rate Improvement: MKT 50:2-3.1
  Resumes: ADM 0:2-8.21.13.2
  Retailing: MKT 0:5
  Retirement: ADM 0:2-8.17
  Retirement, sales: SAL 35:1-4
  Re-Use of Ad Elements: ADV 50:9-11
  Reverse Plates: ADV 50:9-12
  Reverse Culture Shock: IOP 10:3-3
  Right vs. Left Hand Pages: ADV 50:7-6
  ROI (Return on Investment): ADM 0:2-6.1.3
  Rome Report of Business Publication Advertising: ADV 55:1-6
  Rome Report of Expenditures in International Media: ADV 55:2-5
  Ryan Study: ADV 50:5-4.2.1
  S
  Sabbaticals: ADM 0:2-8.4.4
  Safety, product: MKT 35:5
  SALES (See also alphabetized keywords dealing with sales topics; e.g. Women in Selling; Quotas; Territories; etc.): SAL (*)
  Control: SAL 10:5 (*)
  Departments: SAL 10:4 (*)
  Forecasting: MKT 50:2-4 (*)
  Management Training: SAL 10:3
  Manager/Sales Force Relations: SAL 15 (*)
  Manuals: SAL 35:2-1
  Performance, measuring: SAL 10:5-3
  Profession: SAL 5 (*)
  Promotion: SAL 30 (*)
  Aids: SAL 30:3
  Audit/Measurement: SAL 30:4
  Departments, agency: ADV 5:12-5
  Expenditures: Marketing Communications annual reports: SAL 30:1-1
  International: IOP 10:2-13
  Literature: SAL 30:3-1
  Management: MKT 40:1-7
  Role in Marketing: SAL 30:1
  Selling Promotion to Management: SAL 30:2
  Proposals, written: SAL 5:6-7
  Sales & Marketing Management, Survey(s) of Buying Power: MKT 50:2-4.1.2
  Sales & Marketing Management, Survey(s) of Industrial and Commercial Buying Power: MKT 50:2-4.1.3
  Salespeople, distributors' and manufacturers' agents: MKT 20:9-9
  Sampling, in marketing research: MKT 50:2-1.35
  Sampling, new product: MKT 60:2-5
  Scaling: MKT 50:2-1.36
  Scrambled-Marketing: MKT 5:2-12
  Seasonal Advertising: ADV 50:2-5 (*)
  Seasonal Impact, direct mail: ADV 35:3-12
  Seasonal Inquiry Response: ADV 45:1-1
  Second Sales Forces: SAL 10:4-1
  Secretaries: ADM 0:2-7.20
  Secretaries, corporate: ADM 0:2-3
  Security, exhibit: MKT 25:4-5
  Security Values and Advertising: ADV 0:2-2
  Segmentation, marketing: MKT 50:2-4.2 (*)
  Selective and Specialized Selling: SAL 40:13
  Self-Development, salespersons: SAL 5:6 (*)
  Self-Regulation, advertising industry: ADV 25:4
  Sellers' Market, advertising in: ADV 0:3-2
  Selling Management on Industrial Advertising: ADV 0:4-1
  Selling Management on the Value of Research/Information: MKT 50:5
  Selling in Modern Marketing: SAL 0
  Selling Techniques: SAL 40 (*)
  Seminars: ADM 0:2-7.2.5
  Sensitivity Analysis, in research: MKT 50:2-1.37
  Sensitivity Training: ADM 0:2-8.21.11
  Sensorigraphics: MKT 50:2-1.38
  Sequential Analysis: MKT 50:2-1.39
  Service Selling: SAL 40:15
  Setting Advertising Goals and Objectives: ADV 40:1
  Shape of Ad: ADV 50:9-13
  Share of Market, measurement: MKT 50:2-4.3
  Shareholder/Investor Relations: ADM 0:2-10.18
  Shift Method: MKT 50:2-1.40
  Shortage Economy, advertising in: ADV 0:3-2.1
  Shorter Work Week: ADM 0:2-4.12.1
  Show Selection and Participation Procedures: MKT 25:2
  SIC Analysis, circulation: ADV 50:5-4.14
  SIC Analysis, research: MKT 50:2-4.4
  Simulation: 50:2-1.41